So here is your list. I'm not going to go through 145 sites. Some of them are black
sites. Some of them are bases, you know, about like Wright Patterson, Edwards, Nellis, Area 51,
so-called. But all of them are based on witness testimony and intelligence we've gathered over
the last 30 years and it's time for it to be disclosed. Recently in 2024, Stephen Greer in
the Disclosure Project released their entire catalog of documents, communication logs,
drawings, and other files. Love them or hate them, over the years, Greer has provided valuable
witnesses a platform to speak and wrote in my opinion a truly fantastic piece of work,
his 2001 Disclosure Briefing document. So while I have my problems with Greer,
this document archive absolutely commands my attention. Greer's list of UFO whistleblowers
and witnesses features over 700 names, many of which are redacted. Here we find names we all
expect. Michael Herrera, the late Dr. Robert Wood, Richard Doty, Robert Salas, Jonathan Wagan,
even Bob Lazar. But we also find 22 pages of redacted names. Some of these names are described
simply as points of contact to others, but some have descriptions that might be well worth our
attention. Viewers of my channel may remember UFO witnesses redacted list in which I derived the
names and contacted two of these witnesses from poorly redacted documents uploaded by Greer.
One such witness MS agreed to interview on UFO testing occurring at Dugway Proving Grounds while
the other witness TB was much more shadowy. Today we cover the redacted entry that has
captivated my attention and commanded my research for months on end. A witness I have been more than
eager to cover as I believe this witness's alleged first-hand experiences with UFO reverse
engineering offer crucial insights into DOD and defense contractor involvement with UFO programs.
Hey guys it's UAP Gerb and thank you so much for joining me today. I am beyond excited to cover
another witness in Steven Greer's redacted list. Witness 11063 who makes claims of testing UAP
reverse engineer technology and craft at Edwards Air Force Base, California. Grab your pencils and
notebooks because we have a tremendous amount of research to conduct and avenues to explore from
two simple documents on this former wing commander at Edwards. And before we get started guys full
disclaimer I have been able to ascertain this individual's identity and have tried to contact
him through myriad methods. Should he ever respond and be willing to go public I will go to any lengths
to speak with him. But for operational security and his family's safety I will not burn witness
11063's identity. I have also attempted to encourage this individual to testify before
Congress or contact the Senate Intelligence Committee. For this project I will only be using
publicly available sources no classified or hidden information will be disclosed in this video.
And I would like to say I have thoroughly vetted this individual through public online resources
and can confirm his Air Force station at Nellis Air Force Base, Edwards Air Force Base, and the
Pentagon as well as various positions within the U.S. Air Force as stated by Greer.
I first took note of witness 11063 who I will further refer to as Ed when Dr. Greer released
his witness list. This astonishing entry reads quote career Air Force Nellis Edwards test director
of electronics warfare group tested reverse engineer technology was at the Pentagon DOE
Wing commander at Edwards contacted us in 2023 end quote unlike MSTB and myriad other witnesses no
communications or files existed on Ed at the initial release of the DPI archive files.
It wasn't until late summer of 2024 the disclosure project intelligence archive
updated an additional section of documents intelligence briefing modules that we would
get our first leads on Ed within this section we find module three under UFO crash retrievals
titled quote covert government retrieval and handling ET vehicles end quote analyzing the
executive summary we find some fascinating information adapted from a March 2024 oral
presentation from Greer not only does Greer discuss 130 plus instances of NHI objects being
downed and retrieved involving major defense contractors such as Lockheed Martin Skunkworks
and Boeing but these operations are conducted using advanced electrocovidic technologies
and electromagnetic pulse EMP weapons I do highly recommend reading through the entirety of this
module as it invokes the quality of the 2001 disclosure briefing document and also makes
mention of witness MS and Richard Focch a formal naval research lab senior scientist who discussed
large silent triangular alien reproduction vehicles over remote areas of dugway proving grounds
towards the end of module three we see our first discussion of Ed outside the witness list quote
a lieutenant colonel who managed pilots at Edwards Air Force Base and is responsible for training
pilots who operated man-made UFOs has expressed his willingness to share his information openly
Dr. Greer introduced him to the Senate Intelligence and Armed Services Committee
where he shared information he is also eager to testify openly before the House Oversight Committee
though responses from key members like reps Luna and Bershet have not yet been received
having left the Air Force in 2009 the Lieutenant Colonel was extensively briefed on operations
not just at Edwards but also at Nellison area 51 he believes that since the operations he was
involved in were illegal he is free to discuss them publicly and is ready to disclose everything
he knows in an open hearing under oath end quote it was around the time of the upload of this module
Greer finally uploaded two documents under witness 11063
first let's analyze what I would consider to be the less impactful of the two documents on Ed
to understand his background and motives for contacting Greer in late 2023 in presumably an
internal disclosure project email an unknown individual emailed Greer stating witness Ed
had been following Greer's work for some time and wish to answer Greer's call for whistleblowers
this dpi employee states Ed served in USAF from 1999 to his early retirement in 2015
where he ended his career according to the email Ed additionally came from an engineering background
worked with the Department of Energy and served at the Pentagon for seven years the email accurately
breaks down Ed's service record three years at Nellis Air Force Base Nevada three years at
Hanscom Air Force Base Massachusetts and five years at Edwards Air Force Base California in 2006
Ed was sent to Edwards AFB for the bases test pilot school it was here Ed would claim pilots at the
Air Force Base are trained for unacknowledged special access programs using reverse engineered
non-human technology side note Edwards is well known for its prolific and prestigious test pilot
this highly selective program trains pilots navigators and engineers on experimental flight
platforms originating from the Air Force material commands 412th test wing the test pilot school's
mission is to quote conduct full spectrum tests and evaluations of aerospace weapons and to be
the world's premier educational and training center for theoretical and applied flight test
engineering end quote an additional point the test pilot school originated out of Wright Patterson
Air Force Base during World War two during his time at Edwards after graduating the USAF's highly
selective test pilot school Ed would serve as the head of an electronic warfare group that tested
NHI reverse engineered technology in this role Ed claimed to serve as the intermediary between
engineers who had direct reporting to him and test pilots when quote they had a manned craft they
were testing end quote interesting to point out here according to the email Ed agrees with Dr.
Greer stance on free energy systems from direct firsthand involvement in various projects a little
bit of context here since the late 90s early 2000s Greer has highlighted issues of suppressed
technologies and systems levied from the reverse engineering of off world technologies these
technologies are famously referred to as zero point energy systems to quote the 2001 disclosure
document quote we have identified insiders and scientists who can prove in open congressional
hearings that we do in fact possess classified energy generation and anti-gravity propulsion
systems capable of completely and permanently replacing all forms of current used energy
generation and transport systems these devices access the ambient electromagnetic and so called
zero point energy state to produce vast amounts of energy without any pollution such systems
essentially generate energy by tapping into the ever present quantum vacuum energy state the baseline
energy from which all energy and matter is fluxing all matter and energy is supported by this baseline
energy state and it can be tapped through unique electromagnetic circuits and configurations
to generate huge amounts of energy from space time all around us these are not perpetual
motion machines nor do they violate the laws of thermodynamics they merely tap an ambient energy
field all around us to generate energy end quote zero point and free energy systems are not the
topic of today's video so i recommend reading the hunt for zero point by author nick cook jesse
michael's video aerospace secret search for anti-gravity or even greer's 2023 documentary the
lost century and how to reclaim it and it is interesting and worth noting that this internal
disclosure project email states ed is in complete agreement with greer stance on free energy ed isn't
the only witness to comment on zero point systems either take redacted entry 10 747 for example who
is stated to be an x chairman and vp of a well-known corporation i have high conviction this company
is general electric according to greer 10 747 has quote huge details and testimony regarding free
energy and the military industrial complex cover-up slash suppression of these technologies
no several people killed and scared to death end quote towards the end of our witness testimony
internal email mention is made ed had been tracking current legislation relating to legacy program
member amnesty and would be willing to testify to aero as long as kirk patrick was removed from
the organization because according to ed the good doctor quote is an insider and is meant to squash
information end quote this is indeed a very charged statement and one i am sure many ufo
investigators will agree with based off the actions of sean kirk patrick and the way you combat conspiracy
theories and and the associated misunderstandings that fuel them is a fact and science and truth
so if you've got evidence for conspiracy then then that helps to investigate what the underlying truth
is there has been none that has been substantiated for this and everything that has been brought to
our attention and everything that was brought to my attention when i was in that position as the
director we investigated and discovered that it did not come from where they thought it came from
most everything was explainable through other documentation other programs other people that
had talked to other people it goes without saying dr k has very little goodwill with the public
like the lies and half-hearted debunks in the aero historical report volume one or aero's 2022
contracts with sandcorp a company built to plug whistleblower leaks i have even made an entire video
on sean kirk patrick and his disinformation which is at this point somewhat outdated as it covered
little of kirk patrick's role as an unpaid consultant after leaving aero so let's briefly
cover a new revelation that supports ed's accusations of the doctor injecting misinformation
into the public well in a recent us space command foyer release by twitter user tag underscore om
we can find a january 2023 meeting scheduled by dr kirk patrick involving us space com and
senior us joint command staff the purpose of this meeting was quote uap response and recovery and
material transfer end quote the witness testimony document gives us a brief overview of ed his
background and motives but our next document is where our true research can begin
this two-page set of notes roughly covers a phone conversation between dr grier and ed on
november 25th 2023 not only do these notes describe ed's testimony in depth but also break down his
military career by year and station the document is absolutely worth going through line by line
off the bat ed asks rear if he has threatened legal action against lockheed and bowing as ed
was read into programs overlapping these two companies at the beginning of his air force
career ed did indeed work with lockheed as a range technical contractor in the early 2000s at nellis
air force base along with some other smaller specialized contractors however there is no
mention of bowing to the best of my knowledge in his work history publicly we can find myriad
projects and current job openings for work between lockheed and nellis air force base but there are
a few of extreme interest here check out this lockheed martin case study titled the importance
of intelligence surveillance and reconnaissance in which the contractor was tasked with updating
the system used by usaf warfare center for intelligence collection and processing lockheed
martin reconfigured a two-phase security classification system used by the national geospatial
intelligence system yes the same agency grush was a part of when liaison to the uap task force
and the same agency recently mentioned by respected journalist chris sharp as participating in
undersea uap crash retrievals the system was implemented to combined air and space operation
center at nellis air force base which is tasked with processing information for exploitation of
time sensitive targets i can't help but speculate here although this lockheed project arose from
challenges in the nellis red flag advanced aerial combat training exercise could such systems be used
to monitor uap and uap crash retrievals the idea ed was read into uap programs at nellis air force
base as a first lieutenant from 1999 to 2002 can possibly be reinforced later in the notes where
greer states ed was briefed at area 51 s4 where quote a major said they had caught slash captured
lots of aircraft end quote this small point will later become even more interesting as we learn
the area 51 groom lake facility is administered by a detachment from edwards air force base
california the base where ed would transfer to and conduct the bulk of his first hand work around
uap programs ed states this briefing was conducted via a 30 minute video which showed inspection
aircraft that were essentially invisible inspection craft what exactly does this mean is ed referring
to crash retrievals or possibly alien reproduction vehicles arvs for inspection use only this reminds
me closely of the story of mark mcandellish whose close friend brad sorenson allegedly saw three
arvs titled flux liners that were available for cleared personnel to inspect with paneling removed
to highlight hardware of the craft the linings craft were essentially invisible further supports
this thesis as i have covered firsthand witnesses before that have discussed arv craft with cloaking
mechanisms craft that look identical to the flux liner highlighted by mcandellish and an
interesting detail according to sorenson and mcandellish these arvs were shown at norton air
force base a mere 80 miles from edwards air force base if you're unfamiliar with the testimony of
mark mcandellish have no fear i will cover it soon as i believe it is one of the most impactful
testimonies in all of ufology greer goes on to state that at nellis air force base nevada
ed worked at building 200 under the redacted name of the first commander of the 98th range wing now
let's break this down the 98th range wing now called the nevada test and training range began
operations in 2001 and serves as the primary military training area for the nellis air force
base complex to quote usaf the nttr is the largest contiguous air and ground space available for
peacetime military operations in the free world the range occupies 2.9 million acres of land 5000
square miles of airspace which is restricted from civilian air traffic overflight and quote
the nevada test and training range nttr provides the warfighter of flexible realistic and multi
dimensional battle space to conduct testing tactics development and advanced training and
support of us national interests while also conducting department of energy testing research
and development quote the nttr coordinates operational and support matters with major
commands other services do e and department of interior as well as other federal state and
local government agencies the nttr acts as the single point of contact for range customers and
quote analyzing the nttr and its mission to create operate and maintain live and synthetic
environments and integrate partners to optimize warfighter capabilities this location sounds
like an ideal choice for do d and usg elements alongside contractors to test reverse engineer
technology to top it off the nttr south range contains groom lake area 51 a location deeply
entwined with ufology his time at building 200 at the nttr may have seen ed interact with boeing
lachid martin alongside the doe which i mentioned i could find no record of in his resume circling
back to the call notes greer made specific note to ed serving under the first commander right around
2001 of the 98th range wing or nttr i have tried at length and failed to find the original commander
of the 98th but i would like to take a long hard look at the commander from 2005 to 2007
colonel christopher haves i find this analysis necessary as ed may have implied the 98th commander
has oversight to uap reverse engineering programs colonel haves spent 26 years in the air force
linked to key roles in fighter aviation his post service resume is of heavy interest here
following the air force and its service in the 98th range wing haves directed global trade
controls at boeing in washington dc handling trade policy and technology licensing within
major government departments haves additionally led a team at raytheon technologies another defense
contractor implicated with uap study here the colonel managed relationships with key usg officials
such as the office of the secretary of defense and other military departments aligning raytheon
strategies within government objectives the colonel also served as a special advisor on national
security affairs to then vice president dick cheney who has seen swirls of rumors recently
implicating cheney as a senior member of ufo programs where have offered insights on foreign
defense capabilities haves resume as well as his role as commander of the 98th range wing
offers us a glimpse at a possible reverse engineering program official and speaking of the nttr in
greer's notes we can find a simple sentence quote ed saw man-made craft on the range was there quite
a bit end quote with strong conviction we can assume the range in question here is the nttr
from this statement we can also gauge that ed is claiming area 51 slash s4 and or nellis
air force base has successful man-made reverse engineered craft greer then comments on ed being
sent to edwards air force base in california in 2006 for range orientation where ed would go on to
serve as director of redacted for an electronic warfare group referencing the witness testimony
document we can assume this director role was a test director for a technology reverse engineering
group we can also assume from witness testimony this station followed ed's service in edwards
test pilot school what bolsters these claims from ed is the fact edwards electronic warfare group
stems from the 412th test wing the exact same wing that houses the edwards usaf test pilot school
if ed's testimony is true the 412th test wing out of edwards directly deals with the testing of
reverse engineered craft and technology of non-human origin this would also mean the 412th
reverse engineering program works in conjunction with the nevada test in training range this is
one of the biggest takeaways of this entire research project if his testimony is true ed was
briefed on uap programs at s4 while stationed at nellis where he was then sent to the 412th
test pilot school and test wing to further this work in an air force legacy ufo program as a test
director the document state ed served at nellis until 2002 and was then sent to edwards in 2006
where was ed during this gap this period of time 2002 to 2005 saw ed stationed at handscom
air force based near boston massachusetts greer writes that ed worked with the massachusetts
institute of technology while at handscom working on foreign military assets but only saw terrestrial
this mention of mit is still of great interest to us i've talked before about the involvement of
ua rc or university affiliated research centers with uap programs many times most recently with
dr eric a walker head of penn states ua rc the applied research laboratory who admitted he was
involved in the keksburg ufo crash incident while mit has their own ua rc operating under the us
army as well the institute for soldier nano technologies whose goal is to quote discover
and feel technologies that dramatically improve the protection survivability and mission capabilities
of the warfighter and of warfighter supporting platforms and systems and quote the only mention
i can find of relation between handscom and uap is an anonymous letter sent to Leonard
stringfield dated march 14th 1975 which claimed to recount the testimony of one colonel sims a
pseudonym according to the letter both handscom and mit are two of the military bases and research
laboratories that perform ufo operations alongside edwards right paterson carswell los alamos sandia
etc okay so ed served at edwards from 2006 to 2010 where he was allegedly formally read into
multiple quote unquote advanced aircraft programs at edwards the use of the word formal here is
quite interesting almost like ed's time at nellis saw him getting bits and pieces of program
information while his role as test director saw a complete briefing this echoes numerous claims
that uap reverse engineering programs are as if not more compartmentalized than the manhattan
atomic bomb project greer writes in 2008 when director of a redacted program ed was part of a
go public plan via the air force the plan was called off in 2009 to 2010 and saw ed move to the
pentagon the killing of the program was done by a two star general now i have found no confirming
evidence of this so-called go public plan but i have found a series of use of two star generals aka
major generals that either retired as major generals or were at the time period of interest
that may give us an answer one prime suspect is major general thomas k anderson who reached
the rank of major general in 2009 and retired in 2013 anderson's senior role oversaw him
serving as commander of the curtis e lemay center for doctrine development and education
to quote the air force quote the center is responsible for the research development and
production of air force doctrine and input for joint and multinational doctrine development
activities and quote general anderson oversaw numerous key positions within do d such as the
air staff joint staff combat command staffs nato and chief of staff and director of intelligence
for us strategic command let us also inspect major general u jean haas who served as brigadier
general during our window 2009 to 2010 before being promoted to major general in 2012 haas served as
vice commander air force special operations command from 2009 to 2011 haas additionally
acted as director for force structure requirements resources and strategic assessment as a j8 haas
commanded my interest due to his extremely prestigious role within do d and station at
two air force bases allegedly connected to uap programs mac dill air force base and fort belvois
virginia moving on i would like to look at major general kcd blake who earned his major
general ship in 2015 and served as a colonel during ed's alleged disclosure plan not only
did general blake work as commander to air force installations contracting agency of assistant
secretary of the air force for acquisition at right paterson air force base ohio but his most
senior position saw blake as the deputy assistant secretary for contracting under the office of
the assistant secretary for air force for acquisition in washington dc here he was responsible for quote
all aspects of contracting relating to the acquisition of weapon systems logistics and
operational support for the air force end quote overseeing support of 826 billion dollars annually
although blake may have been a colonel during this plan he piqued my interest as during 2008 he
served as director program acquisitions defense procurement and acquisition policy in the office
of the under secretary of defense for acquisition technology and logistics for the pentagon there
are a total of four other major generals of interest here including c donald allston h brent
blake senior randy ap but i want to lastly focus on major general christopher p asano asano did not
earn his major general ship until 2019 meaning during 2009 to 2010 he is the least likely
candidate to have decision-making power over a disclosure campaign however his early career
dovetails almost identically with that of ed and is worth mentioning in the year 2000 asano attended
usav test pilot school at you guessed it edwards in the early 2010s the general would command the
412th operations group at edwards before serving as the commander of the air force test center at
edwards at his senior station asano oversaw a 31 billion dollar enterprise comprised of more than
19 000 military civilian and contractor personnel across edwards aigland and arnold afb's greer
makes special note to right paterson air force base the infamous location we have discussed in
almost every single video i have ever done according to ed right paterson has a tight
connection with edwards ed even makes an educated guess right pat's hangar six specifically held
by a logics according to internal right pat documents hangar six was initially quote primarily
used by the signal corps for installing radios and antennas and after the war it became a facility
for retrofitting and modifying planes and quote the hangar featured several smaller doors instead
of a giant hangar door which would later be used as the right field fitness center however the fitness
center is located in hangar 22 not hangar six at right pat besides blueprints and images of the
exterior i can find almost zero internal images reports or articles in general on hangar six
this facility will be a priority of my research moving forward especially analyzing for infrastructure
to support living and or deceased biologics as ed has claimed from 2010 to 2015 following the failed
coming forward plan ed moved to the pentagon where according to greer he operated within research
and development panel chain little was discussed between greer and ed on his responsibilities
at the pentagon however one interesting note is recorded quote 34 billion dollars than 40 billion
dollars to non air force authorization non blue toa and quote toa meaning transfer of authority
this statement seemingly confirms statements made over the decades by numerous whistleblowers
discussing uap programs being funded through usap off book black operations i will draw your attention
to december 11th 2017 where former assistant secretary of housing and urban development
kathryn austin fits published a paper titled black budget of the united states here she discussed
21 trillion dollars found in unauthorized spending in the department of defense and
housing and urban development centers between 1998 and 2015 soon after publication the dod
announced its first ever department wide independent audit fits personally believed
some unauthorized funding was utilized for domestic clandestine military rnd some of
legal uap programs from dod
the primary testimony of ed involves first-hand work on uap programs focused on the testing
of reverse engineered non-human technology at nellis air force base slash area 51 s4
and the 412th test group out of edwards air force base california as we have discussed before
numerous factors including ed being briefed at s4 and then sent to the 412th for test pilot
school before becoming director of the electronic warfare group where he acted as the intermediary
between engineers and test pilots when the group had manned craft to test we can conclude with
high confidence ed's work revolved primarily around the utilization of nhi tech to construct
and test arv or alien reproduction vehicles area 51 s4 has been discussed in ufology for decades
and is often immediately associated with the claims of bop lasar but what about edwards
are there any other stories of uap programs at the californian base that can support or detract
from ed's claims well for starters we can go all the way back to 1957 to the testimony of mercury
astronaut gordon cooper cooper claimed while stationed as a project manager at edwards air
force base a group of photographers assigned to photograph remote positions of the base
observed a large strange-looking craft above a lake bed cooper's crew began taking films of
the craft and according to cooper the craft was quote hovering above the ground and then it slowly
came down and sat on the lake bed for a few minutes end quote the camera crew estimated the
object to be about 30 feet in diameter shiny silver in color and featured three landing gear
the crew got within 20 yards of the craft before it departed cooper did in fact see the film but
stated the evidence was confiscated and this is a very brief summary of the story as i would love
to cover it further in great detail well that was i was found i was having some camera men found the
installation of a of a precision landing facility we were putting in right on the edge of the dry
lake and the saucer flew right over them and put down three little gear and landed out on the dry
lake bed and they went out to pick up their cameras and moved on out toward him filming
and he left it off put the gear back in the well and climbed out a very high rate of speed and
disappeared and so while i was going through all the regulation books and finding out the number
to call and watching to report it i had to go over and develop the film the time they got back
with the developed film i was on the higher and higher and higher level officer talking to me
finally with the colonel telling me to you know when the film arrived at my desk to put it in the
carrier pouch there would be a courier there at my office by that time already and they'd range for
him to fly in our base airplane back to washington with these films and uh do not run prints etc etc
etc so we stuck them in the courier pouch did you watch the film we didn't have a chance to run it i
had a chance to hold it up to the window and look at it it was certainly a good film good close-up
good close-up shot in 1972 we can find project outgrowth out of the usaf rocket propulsion
lab at edwards a document titled advanced propulsion concepts project outgrowth
sees discussion of an anti-gravity program and theoretical material to change the direction
and amplitude of gravitational fields similarly in 1988 a technical report submitted under
contract with the usaf aeronautics lab out of edwards discusses the exploration of the
bifield brown effect explored at length by jessie michaels which allegedly converts
electrostatic energy into propulsion around the same year 1988 defense contractor science
applications international corporation saic a defense contractor i have directly implicated
in the study of off-world technologies studied similar electronic propulsion mechanisms for
edwards air force base we can also look to 1990 where journalist scott williams wrote an article
in aviation week in which 45 sightings of aircraft accelerating from near hovering positions to
supersonic speeds were seen over edwards air force base george air force base in china lake
naval weapons center one such craft was described as triangular in shape but let's not forget the
1998 testimony of usaf master sergeant edgar foush i have covered numerous times who commented on the
infamous tr 3b reverse engineered triangular craft foush claimed while working at the defense
advanced research board in 1979 under the jet propulsion laboratory at edwards a full anti-gravity
propulsion system was developed and a secret space fleet utilized this technology if you haven't
yet please watch my video on locking martin as i discussed the foush case in much greater depth
including his station at the proposed defense advanced research center while discussing the tr
3b craft foush makes specific mention graduates from the 412th test pilot school at edwards
air force base pilot these reverse engineered craft many more enigmatic claims without direct
evidence exists surrounding edwards the infamous base was mentioned myriad times within lenard
stringfield's crash retrieval status reports 1 through 7 in ufo crash retrievals the inner
sanctum status report 6 stringfield makes mention of a doctor epigoni a pseudonym for a physicist
who claimed to have worked closely with oppenheimer einstein and teller epigoni stated in the late
60s early 70s he worked on something called project heaven a special projects at edwards
air force base the doctor claimed a flying saucer and its crew had previously landed
at edwards the craft was kept in a large hanger guarded tightly whilst occupants were carted off
to a secure building for evaluation the 12 five foot tall bodies clad in silvery metal suits featured
eyes of one color a nose a mouth teeth and blood similar to the appearance of oil to quote epigoni
they the u.s researchers came to the conclusion that since there was no deterioration to leave
them alone because another craft might come in the area and rejuvenate or reactivate them
end quote the craft itself had no rivets seams or welding and was of a classic saucer design with
a dome on top measuring 40 feet in diameter other scientists informed epigoni craft materials
were made of materials they never dreamed could exist and could not figure out a way to gain
entry to the craft epigoni stated as of 1990 project blue heaven was still active it was run
by the dod and the navy had two to three similar projects the doctor's account is far more detailed
and i promise we will circle back to this testimony in future projects but the landing of this craft
and seemingly inert bodies reminds me closely of the craft donation theory when you say crash
retrieval what do you make these are retrieving non-human origin uh technical vehicles you know
call it spacecraft if you will non-human exotic origin vehicles that have either landed or crashed
we have spacecraft from another species we do yeah how many quite a number you're kidding no the
strangest detail of this testimony is the claim the craft touched down the beans walked out of
the craft and laid on the ground it's worth noting and stringfield commented on this too
epigoni changed the body count from 12 to 4 according to stringfield and his fellow investigator
they quote agreed that it appeared that he had consulted with his superiors and was advised to
alter certain key details end quote also in 1991 status report six stringfield recounts his discussions
with a firsthand witness to a ufo crash retrieval 15 miles outside of edwards in 1971 according to
witness debbie clayton her and her girlfriend's family investigated a crash from the sky in broad
daylight reaching the craft site debbie observed an acorn-shaped craft with an extremely similar
description to the kexburg crash quote we searched for markings but found only some old scratches
that we could not read because it was upright we couldn't see the bottom there were no windows
or seams appearing to be made from a one-piece mold if i remember correctly it was a dark grayish
color with greenish highlights not a color one normally sees there was a mild heat coming from
the craft somewhat like a car engine after traveling for an hour one more thing i thought
was strange there was no dust that clung to the shell here in the desert dust is everywhere
and clings to everything end quote according to debbie an air force car and truck arrived within
14 minutes where men with rifles ordered civilians off scene lastly i want to cover an excerpt michael
schratt discovered in the files of the late stringfield which may allow us to directly connect
edwards to operating arv and ny craft alongside area 51 s4 in a letter dated april 5th 1980
one mr d l dobs discussed one mh a witness identity schratt chose not to disclose mh had
allegedly performed radio maintenance at the atomic proving ground in nevada during 1961 to 1963
along with top secret radio work for usaff according to mh he participated in a top secret
operation at area 51 titled project red light test flights were conducted on a recovered ufo
ship from none other than edwards air force base the craft was not conventionally powered
and stayed silent during operation security was so tight on the project program personnel were
rotated every six months mh claimed to have heard rumors of a west coast american defense contractor
encountering difficulties in many of the components comprising the craft
and lastly guys i want to cover a possible connection between reverse engineering programs
at edwards and nella slash area 51 in july of 1991 an alleged classified nr o document leaked to
the public this document informed need to know groups and operations about civilian flying
saucer organizations organizing protests in nevada steven greer claimed to have given the
document to admiral thomas wilson from the wilson davis memo which at the very least we can confirm
the meeting between greer and wilson allegedly wilson told greer he recognized one of the entities
listed and that it was run by a contractor addressed in this document includes royal ops cosmic ops
mage ops magi ops multiple usaf special forces divisions in the 26th 64th 65th 527th nella's
afos i groom lake and dreamland area 51 s4 aquatec and sea spray special operations group
and one blackjack team according to dr steven greer inside sources including a source inside
blackjack control told him of two entities blackjack control and blackjack team blackjack control is
allegedly a nella's based facility participating in reverse engineering while blackjack team
operates in conjunction with control but is stationed at edwards air force base so but the
key facilities i want to go through and there are others this is a list um that i've updated i
updated it um for the president in 09 um a very chief one is edwards air force base and there's
a whole constellation there haystack butte china lakes george air force base they retired norton
air force base tabletop mountain observatory which is run ostensibly by nasa and blackjack control
though i had a source at blackjack control associated with the edwards related facilities
but the blackjack team you saw on that list was nella's so there's blackjack control and blackjack
team i can find almost nothing publicly available to research on blackjack besides a late 2010s
early 2020s project between darpa the defense advanced research project and defense contractors
owned by raytheon project blackjack was quote intended to develop and demonstrate critical
elements of a global high-speed network in low earth orbit that satisfied dod performance and
payload requirements at a much lower cost with shorter design cycles and with easier and more
frequent technology upgrades and quote seen as the alleged nro document dates back to 1991 i doubt
these two blackjacks connect what's going on guys it's uap gerb and i'd like to thank each
and every single one of you for joining me today as we took a deep dive into ed's witness testimony
now i know i discussed this a multitude of times throughout today's video but i'd like to reiterate
today's thesis once more for a final time analyzing ed's credible witness testimony
conclusions can be drawn of a joint reverse engineering program focused on craft of non-human
intelligence existing between edwards air force base california and nella's air force base nevada
slash area 51 s4 this program stems out of the 412th test group comprising the edwards
usaf test pilot school and edwards 412th electronics warfare group now this research was
some of the most enticing exciting and interesting i have done since working on the off-world
technologies division and i would like to compare these two testimonies the off-world
technologies division and the technology here focused more on singular pieces of technology
and almost weapons as described by r.a. now it was interesting to see the juxtaposition between
this air force testimony as the air force plants in conjunction with a lockheed martin bowing and
possibly other contractors actually work on the piloting and utilization of reverse engineered
craft whether these craft are triangular in shape the classic tr 3b as proposed by fauche
or possibly the flux liner classic saucer shape as proposed by mark mcandalish that were housed at
allegedly housed at dormant air force base 1988 i'm not sure perhaps it's both but the line that
fauche states that these pilots put commanded the reverse engineer tr 3b is out of edwards air
force base pilot test uh test school jumped out to me after covering him so long ago in my lockheed
martin video this research was fascinating i wish we could find out a little more on ed's time at
the pentagon all we really have to go off there is the 34 billion dollars and then 40 billion
dollars missing in uh transfer of authorization funds off book funds this can possibly support
greers and other people's thesis that many of these programs are funded through black budget
operations i know that this uh program at at edwards edwards is a very populous base so
if this reverse engineering program is indeed real this must be kept to an exclusively small
number of personnel in an exclusively small area who knows perhaps edwards is connected to
underground facilities in this region i know greer likes to say that the uh anthill facility he
posted a picture of recently in the uh helendale facility are done location so possibly this is a
kind of a connected area in which craft are stored after hearing ed's testimony what do you guys
think i would like nothing more than to speak to ed firsthand and hear all this information
from himself but unfortunately he has gone off books there is no way to contact this individual
whether by phone social media or email and believe me i have tried so if greer is right and this
individual has tested revealed testified revealing information he knows this testimony is indeed
impactful beyond belief but has he or is that one of greer's embellishments we don't know
i'd like more than anything to see this individual ed before the senate intelligence
committee or at november's open hearings who knows maybe we'll be surprised to do so but
let me know what you guys think about this alleged reverse engineering program at uh
edwards air force base and nellis air force base area 51 again if anybody has any other further
research to let me know about this i would love to know i know that uh i drew a conclusion i decided
not to keep it in the video about the air force plant 42 near palm dale sightings of late and
edwards these two facilities are only about 30 miles apart which uh you know very interesting i
think edwards and norton are also only about 80 miles apart so this whole complex is deeply entwined
to both ufo sightings and testimonies of reverse engineering programs i was also thrilled to be
able to dive into the work of lennard stringfield and others to look at some more occasions i know
we uh researched the debbie clayton acorn-shaped craft 15 miles outside of edward that was
immediately swarmed by usaff crew within 15 minutes and the testimony of dr epigoni that
one is very interesting uh relating to the craft donation theory if you don't know what that is
certain individuals like david grush have discussed that some retrievals of uap are not
crash retrievals these craft are just found left unattended this story reminded closely of the
alleged 1957 hollamann air force base landing in which a flying saucer saucer touched down at
hollamann air force base and occupants walked out of the craft to interact with usaff personnel
in epigoni's case these beings walked out of the craft to lay down on the ground and seemingly
turned themselves off which could possibly attest to the the theory of biological robots
essentially as many people like to call the grays there will be further research that needs to be
done on blackjack team and blackjack control this just rang a note in my head from that 1991
alleged nro document but more research needs to be done here thus far i can find no connections
between darpa really but this to me is the jumping off point of researching usaff legacy and contractor
reverse engineering programs possibly housed at contractor sites possibly housed at air force
base locations so let me know what you guys think i really appreciate everybody joining me today
please remember to like and subscribe uh share these videos around i got a patreon if you want to
join i don't charge for any extra content i don't gate keep content all of my research is free for
anybody to consume i only have the patreon if you want to support what you think the channel's worth
but guys i have some awesome upcoming other projects on arvs or alien reproduction vehicles
including a deep dive on mark mcandalish which i hope to do soon i know that's been highly requested
and i cannot wait to do so so without further ado guys i want to thank you all again for joining me
and very soon we'll be back up with another show so thank you very much guys and i'll catch you all
later bye