I thought it was totally nuts and I thought at first I was being deceived, it was a ruse.
People started confiding in me, they approached me, I have plenty of current former senior
intelligence officers that came to me, many of which I knew almost my whole career, that
confided in me they were a part of a program, they named the program, I've never heard
of it.
Forget little green men, forget Area 51, forget Bob Lazar, and get any sort of conspiracy
out of your mind for just a second.
It's no longer just speculation or even a secret that within the US Department of Defense
lies a shadowy UFO reverse engineering and crash retrieval program with access so exclusive,
only a couple hundred people in the 80 plus year history of the program has ever been
read in.
People like David Grush and legislation like Schumer's 2024 NDAA legacy programs have
helped turn a former conspiracy into an outrageous fact.
Sometimes it feels like details, names, and operations of these programs will never come
to life, that those in the know in the defense industry will cling to secrecy until they're
dying breaths.
Though actually receiving transparency may sometimes feel like a distant fever dream,
you know your host UAP Gerb has you.
Join me today and we will venture into Project Moondust and follow the astounding paper trail
of one possible DOD UFO crash retrieval program.
Edward J. Ruppelt conducted the first ever official US government study into the UFO phenomena
under Project Grudge in 1948 to 1949.
He went on to serve as the director of Project Sign and Blue Book, the subsequent US government
official UFO investigation programs in the 20th century.
During his time as director, Ruppelt concluded UFOs had a quote interplanetary explanation.
On the 24th of April 1952, Ruppelt suggested programs parallel to the official USG investigation
were quote, conducting a more complete investigation.
This same conclusion was derived by J. Allen Heineck, the scientific advisor to Project
Blue Book.
We talked about him in the alien and UFOs obscure oddities iceberg layer two, so if you want
to know more, read there.
But Heineck additionally said that alongside Blue Book, there were other classified programs
going on studying UFOs.
One of these projects could have been an inconspicuous crash retrieval program, one
that unless you look hard enough, you'll never know existed, and that of course is
Project Moondust.
The first mention of Moondust can be traced back to 1961 in a US Air Force document titled
AFCIN-1E-0 Draft Policy.
This proposal suggests that the USAF 1127th received collection responsibility duties
for the USAF's established program for investigation of reliably reported unidentified flying objects
within the United States.
The memo also lists one project that has historically had this duty.
That project is Moondust, which has the authority to locate, recover, and deliver descended
foreign space vehicles.
And as we can see in this 1967 review for the Assistant Chief of Staff for the Intelligence
Community, which details the functions of the 1127th USAF Field Activities Group, Moondust
is shown to not just be a proposal, but exists, and has historically dealt with some terrestrial
space vehicles.
In fact, in the 1967 year, Moondust captured a total of 49 fallen Soviet space objects
and 17 US space objects.
And this is followed by a large redacted portion of the memo.
Now we know that Moondust had real collection responsibilities with Soviet American and
redacted space vehicles.
So let's start to take a look at some of Moondust's work.
As early as 1961, Moondust was in fact investigating UFOs and acting on UFO reports.
In this internal memo, in Pakistan, on April 25, 1961, Moondust recorded observations of
three cigar-shaped UFOs flying in a close delta formation above Karachi, Pakistan.
But Moondust wasn't just investigating UFO reports.
In fact, it was actively engaged in UFO collection.
Let's travel to 1968 in Nepal.
In this memo, the Defense Intelligence Department monitors a crashed circular metal disc discovered
in Nepal.
Four months after, the State Department cable titled Moondust, right to the DIA, 1127th,
and Wright-Patterson Air Force Base that a diplomatic visit to Kathmandu, Nepal, was
a, quote, fishing expedition for info on space objects.
Additional cables show Royal Nepali Army showed photos of these space objects to US offices.
A possible cover story was then constructed here of a crashed satellite, despite NORAD
and NASA data showing a 100% successful satellite launch rate in 1968.
Unfortunately the trail stops here, so I cannot tell you if this circular metal disc was actually
recovered by US entities.
Now let's fast forward a little bit to the 1970s.
In Canada in 1976, a memo achieved via the Freedom of Information Act shows that Moondust
wrote to Canadian officials requesting photos of space-related metals originating from
a non-US, quote, satellite.
That would be of particular interest to USF foreign technology divisions at Wright-Patterson
Air Force Base and to the CIA's Office of Weapon Intelligence.
Now Canada has historically been very open on investigating UFOs and participating in
UFO analysis with other Five Eyes nations, but that is another video for another day.
I want you to take particular note of the last two entries and how various memos and
cables have been written to Wright-Patterson Air Force Base.
If you remember an entry from Layer 2 of the Alien and UFOs of Skiur-Ottodies Iceberg,
you remember that Wright-Patterson Air Force Base is connected with the phenomena.
Wright-Patterson is often seen as a hub where crash retrievals of UFOs are stored.
Think of the Roswell case.
Allegedly, the crash materials were sent to Wright-Patterson Air Force Base.
And think of Senator Barry Goldwater, who asked Wright-Patterson officials to see the
room where, quote, it was stored and was laughed off and told never to ask again.
Now if we fast forward to 1978 in New Zealand, Moondust investigates space fragments found
in New Zealand described as spherical or like a pressure vessel.
Note how this pressure vessel shape is very similar to Commander David Fraver's tic-tac
sighting, in which he describes the craft he observed as similar to a propane tank or
pressure vessel without any inlets or outlets.
And finally we arrive at my favorite case involving Project Moondust.
Everybody has heard about the Roswell crash.
Now not everybody knows most countries have their own sort of Roswell story in which some
sort of anomalous craft has hit the ground and some sort of retrieval is underway.
You can think of Canada's Shag Harbor for instance, maybe I'll make a video on Roswells
around the world if you're interested, but you may have never heard of the 1978 Bolivia
UFO crash.
This alleged retrieval was brought to my attention by the work of the UAP Caucus, a legislative
group on UAP initiative backed by members of Congress including Representative Timbershet,
Rep Anna Paulina Luna, Rep Eric Bertelsen, and Rep Jared Moskowitz.
The story famous in Bolivia goes.
On May 6, 1978 at 4.15pm, thousands of people near El Tayer Bolivia witnessed a cylindrical
object crash into the mountainside, creating a sonic boom that was heard up to 150 miles
away and cracked window panes as far as 30 miles in radius.
A local army corporal named Natalio Ruiz actually witnessed the UFO.
Sane flew above his head and resembled a gigantic wine container emitting a trace of white smoke.
Bolivian military and three jets were dispatched to check the wreckage.
Upon discovering the wreckage, the local military and police were quoted as sane.
Our men have discovered the object and inspected it, but have received no further instruction
or further action.
It is a dull metallic cylinder, 12 feet long with a few dents.
No one knows what is inside it, and we are waiting the arrival of various technical commissions.
A NASA expert is also expected to arrive tomorrow morning.
And of course, two U.S. Army Air Force officers, Colonel Robert Simmons and Major Jesse Hayes,
arrived.
Subsequently, secret documents finally obtained through the Freedom of Information Act were
sent to U.S. Secretary of State Cyrus Vance.
In this document, Vance writes that appropriate government agencies have been contacted regarding
this crash.
And I'm sure that you can guess the appropriate agency, Moondust.
Moondust received a film showing the object by the Bolivian military, and were tasked
with monitoring the situation.
Unfortunately, the trail of Moondust's involvement with this fascinating case ends here.
I don't know if they retrieved this craft or did nothing else.
I don't know.
And it absolutely eats at me that I can't find out what happened.
Let's skip forward to 1992.
New Mexico Senators Jeff Bingaman and Pete Domenici made inquiries to the Air Force about
Project Moondust.
In response, the Air Force said that there is no Project Moondust.
These missions have never existed.
The Senators responded with documents challenging this, and the Air Force revised its previous
statement acknowledging the existence and function of Moondust with regards to UFOs.
Then in 1994, Senator Domenici requested 11 documents pertaining to Moondust from the
Air Force.
The Air Force claimed that the projects no longer existed, nor do their files.
Classified reports that may have possibly existed were destroyed.
But this is categorically false.
Why would the Air Force state that documents had been destroyed when requested by a U.S.
Senator?
Why did the Air Force deny the existence of Project Moondust?
And why did they cling on to claiming that any record of the program was destroyed?
I've thought about this.
And do you remember in the Wilson Davis video, when Admiral Thomas Wilson claims that in
the early 90s, special access programs were reorganized to hide the crash retrieval and
reverse engineering programs within SAPOX, basically making them inaccessible to everybody?
When did these Senators ask for documents on Moondust, the mid-90s?
Were these documents destroyed and any sort of involvement denied by the Air Force occur
because of this reorganization and compartmentalization of programs?
I think so.
It's also important to note that in this time from 1969 to 2008, Project Blue Book to
OSAP, there was no official U.S. government UAP investigation group.
So this is what I'd like to consider the dark ages, the completely hidden era of UFO
investigation.
The Air Force clung on to denying the existence of Moondust.
And that is where our paper trail ends.
It's quite plausible that the Air Force destroyed the majority of files pertaining to Moondust.
In order to hide a crash retrieval program of UFOs.
My friends, thank you for joining me to take a look through Project Moondust.
I hope you learned something today.
I hope you learned that, you know, even though sometimes it may seem impossible to crack
what the United States government and defense industry and intelligence industry have been
up to in regards to UFOs, it is possible with enough digging.
I want to know in the comments what you guys think.
Do you think Moondust has historically been, or was at least at one point, responsible
for collecting UAP, or do you think it was just involved in collecting foreign and domestic
space vehicles because I do not?
I absolutely do not.
There's a couple other programs such as Zodiac, Blue Fly, the CIA's Office of Global Access,
and a couple more unacknowledged programs I'd like to cover in the future, so stay tuned
for that.
But please, if you don't mind, give a like and subscribe, it really helps the channel
and I am astounded at how this community has grown so far.
It's incredible to see people with the same passion for UFOs that I have kind of engaged
in the comments and watch these videos, so I gotta give you my deepest gratitude, because
I am forever thankful.
I will catch you guys for the next video, and thank you for tuning in, bye.